<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>midnight solarium</title>
		<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org</link>
		<description>a website dedicated to all organisms, formations, and concepts that grow in the night</description>
		<item>
			<title>28.04.25</title>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">updating to distract myself from the cdn election</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org</link>
			<description>mostly a CSS update: toned down overlay effect and remove most page transitions, reduced mobile layout jank, tweaked global and landing page styling, removed landing page link to the old version of site, also i guess im on fediverse now so i added that link</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>11.04.25</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">imadeitworse</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/weblog</link>
			<description>wrote a weblog post about Usenet and maybe some other stuff too, added more buttons to links page (this was long overdue; sorry y'all!), changed the flower icon and index page logo, made wilde.AI more cartoonishly evil, tweaked some recipes, changed the weblog page layout, made minor css changes to homepage, made index page more succinct</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>09.03.25</title>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">wilde.ai and starpants</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/garden/wildeai</link>
			<description>launched poetry generator wilde.AI (which is a totally real AI! source: trust me), added ☆.⋆~star pants~⋆.☆ to craft catalog, hung decorative lights on landing page</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>16.02.25</title>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">baby blankets and anti-love letters</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/weblog_posts/i_dont_want_to_fall_in_love</link>
			<description>wrote a somewhat off-the-cuff weblog about my messy relationship with Valentine's Day, edited some links on previous weblog, added baby blanket to craft catalog, removed carbon counter because it wasn't working properly, fixed css on landing page</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>12.02.25</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">slight layout tweaks and also some moths</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/home</link>
			<description>tweaked layout to require less divs and look a bit less visually cluttered, made a new button, wrote more ruminations, wrote a brief weblog about a graphics resource i found</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>31.01.25</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">stackoverflow did not come through for me so i had to write my own javascript for once</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/garden/ruminations</link>
			<description>created chaos garden (meant to be a hub for misc. webpages that don't fit anywhere else), made ruminations page, tweaked rss so hopefully it'll show up on nekoweb's built-in feed, tweaked layout to be a bit friendlier to smaller and medium-sized screens</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>20.01.25</title>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">is this how you make an RSS feed?</guid>
			<link>https://midnightsolarium.nekoweb.org/home</link>
			<description>finally slapped together an RSS feed (which you are reading right now! assuming i did it right!), retroactively added lazyloading to some image-heavy pages, added new slippers to craft catalog, added more notes to notebook, added one easter egg (good luck!)</description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>